# JESSICA DEL ROSARIO

204.894.1438 / jessicalimdr@gmail.com / www.linkedin.com/in/jessicalimdelrosario / https://jessicadr.github.io/

#### **PROFILE**

I strive to create effective yet attractive design solutions for problems that will improve lives. With a passion for design across all mediums and an academic background in behavioural neuroscience, I found the perfect integration of my skills in UX research/design.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **UBC Launch Pad - UX/UI Designer**

Vancouver, BC

September 2019 - Current

- UBC Launch Pad is a student-run software engineering team devoted to building software projects in a collaborative, professional environment
- Collaboratively conducting user research, creating wireframes, prototyping, user testing, and branding
- Effectively communicating with a team of developers, business strategists, and designers, while iterating upon feedback

#### Sprouts @ nwHacks - UX/UI Designer

Vancouver, BC

January 2020

- Within 24 hours, designed and conducted user research for an iOS app that helps users take care of their plants and reduce stress level
- Created high-fidelity designs, interactive prototypes and conducted user tests to validate designs
- Collaborated with a team of developers and created a high-quality product presentation despite the time constraint

#### MoneyBee @ cmd-f - UI Designer

Vancouver, BC

March 2020

- Within 24 hours, designed an Android mobile app to empower young women through financial education using innovative games
- Ideated with a team of designers and developers
- Designed educational mini-games, branding, and presentation

# **UBC Student Communications Services - UX Researcher** Vancouver, BC

April 2019 - September 2019

- Used mixed user tests and interviews to identify issues and create solutions for users interacting with UBC online platforms
- Produced full case studies, research presentations, and analyzed user data
- Reported to designers for future improvements and changes

## **SKILLS**

#### **Design and Research**

Prototyping
Sketching and Storyboarding
User Interviews
Contextual Inquiry
Persona and Scenario Development
Usability Testing
Data analysis
Wireframing

#### **Technical**

HTML/CSS, Sketch, InVision, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Adobe Premiere, JavaScript, Procreate

# **EDUCATION**

#### **University of British Columbia**

Vancouver, BC September 2017 - Current - Bachelor of Science, Behavioural Neuroscience

# **AWARDS**

#### First Place - cmd-f 2020

- Created MoneyBee, an app that empowers young women through financial education using innovative games

#### Third Place - BizHacks 2020

- Created Blue Pocket, an Android app extension, with a team of developers, ranking Third Place out of 100+ teams

# **Emergent BioSolutions Award**Global Specialty Life Sciences Company 2017

 Outstanding academic performance in sciences and commitment to the local community